莉莉丝才是最后一道封印
Lilith was the final seal.
而我杀了她就等于是我亲手释放了路西法
I killed her, and I set Lucifer free.
你们这群二愣子才是推动审判之日到来的幕后黑手
You sons of bitches jump-started judgment day!
天启已经降世了
It's Apocalypse now.
拉斐尔 他在哪儿
Raphael, where is he?
上帝吗 他早死了 卡西迪奥
God? he's dead, Castiel.
你知道我的身份
You know who am I?
路西法
Lucifer.
非你莫属啊 萨姆 你才是我真正的皮囊
You're the one, Sam. you're my true vessel.
那是绝不可能的事儿
That never happen.
你是米迦勒之剑
You're the Michael sword.
- 米迦勒之剑啥意思 - 你是米迦勒的皮囊
- What do you mean, I'm the sword? - You're Michael's weapon.
- 我就是具皮囊 - 独一无二的皮囊
- I'm a vessel? - You're the vessel.
你们对付的是恶作剧的精灵
You got a trickster on your hands.
那究竟是个啥玩意儿 幽灵还是恶魔
So, what is it … spirit, demon?
确切而言算是个半神
More like demigod.
他们长生不老
They're immortal,
他们可以制造出无中生有的事物
And they can create things out of thin air,
通常还会带点儿黑色幽默 来点儿致命的恶作剧
Usually with a sense of humor … deadly pranks.
得 鲍比忽略了一个细节
Okay, another thing Bobby mentioned.
这家伙绝对是个十足的甜食爱好者
Was that these suckers have a real sweet tooth.
对你而言这很有趣吗
So this is fun for you?
用不同方式一次次地杀死迪恩
Killing Dean over and over again?
萨姆 这不过是给你上一课罢了
Sam, there's a lesson here.
- 上什么课 - 提醒你 迪恩是你的软肋
- What lesson? - Dean's your weakness.
所有的敌人也都知道这一点
The bad guys know it, too.
而他迟早会为你牺牲 萨姆
He's gonna be the death of you, Sam.
《凶鬼恶灵》是直接在观众面前表演的情景剧
"Supernatural" is filmed before a live studio audience.
看来我需要张再大点儿的嘴才行啊
I'm gonna need a bigger mouth.
嘿 萨姆 怎么啦
Hey, there, Sam. what's happening?
没事
Oh, nothing.
只是世界末日而已
Um… just the end of the world.
你需要张再大点儿的嘴才行啊
You're gonna need a bigger mouth.
嘿 你负责研究的那块搞定了吗
Hey, uh…have you done your research yet?
那当然
Oh, yeah.
所有的研究都搞定了 做了一宿
All kinds of research. all night.
是吗
Yeah?
迪恩
Oh, Dean…
我们似乎还有很多研究要完成噢
…we have some more "research" to do.
迪恩
Dean…
我靠
Son of a bitch!
（惠灵顿 俄亥俄州）
（两天前）
医生
Doctor…
你在看什么呢
What are you watching?
一个医务剧
It's a hospital show.
《性感医生》我觉得应该改拍自一本书
"Dr. Sexy, M.D." I think it's based on a book.
居然你也看这种剧 更年期到了吗
When did you hit menopause?
不过是无意间转到就顺便看看罢了
It's called channel-surfing.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
你呢
Are you?
再确认一次 是什么风把联邦调查局吹来了呢
One more time … the F.B.I is here why, exactly?
噢 我们是来调查
Well, it might have something to do.
这里的一个当地居民的断头事件的
With one of your locals getting his head ripped off.
比尔·伦道夫是因熊的袭击而毙命的
Bill Randolph died from a bear attack.
你们有多肯定那一定是熊造成的
How sure are you that it was a bear?
否则还能是什么
What else would it be?
无论是什么
Well, whatever it was,
那东西都追着伦道夫先生穿过了森林
It chased Mr. Randolph through the woods,
并撞开了他的前门 跟着他上了二楼
Smashed through his front door, followed him up the stairs,
最后将他杀死在卧室里
And killed him in his bedroom.
这都合乎常理吗 一只熊能办到这一切
Is that common … a bear doing all that?
我猜这取决于它是否被彻底激怒了那熊
Depends how pissed off it is, I guess.
听着 伦道夫一家住在森林的腹地
Look, the Randolphs lived way up in high country.
你们要去的地方能足以吓哭一个成年男人
You got trout runs that'll make a grown man weep…
那里还有熊
And bears.
明白 现在伦道夫太太怎么样了
Right. now, what about Mrs. Randolph?
档案里说她目睹了这个事件的发生
The file says she saw the whole thing.
是的 没错 我非常地同情那位可怜的女士
Yes, she did. my heart goes out to that poor woman.
是她说的熊吗
She said bear?
凯西·伦道夫刚刚才经历丧夫之疼
Kathy Randolph went through a hell of a trauma.
尚有点儿神智不清
She's confused.
她到底说了些什么
What did she say?
不 那绝对是只熊
No. i-it must have been a bear.
否则 还能是什么呢
I-I mean, what else could it have been?
伦道夫太太
Mrs. Randolph…
你觉得那是什么
What did you think it was?
是的 我到现在都很清晰地记得
No. I-I remember clearly now.
那的的确确是一只熊
It was definitely a bear.
我们也这么认为
We're sure it was.
但是 我们需要多收集线索 从各个角度
But see, it … it helps us to hear, uh, every angle.
所以 不妨大方地说说你的所见和所想吧
So, just tell us what you thought you saw.
好吧 虽然这不大可能 但
Well, it's impossible, but…
我可以发誓我看到了
…I could have sworn I saw…
绿巨人
…The incredible hulk.
The incredible hulk.
我早说过了 这很疯狂
I told you. it's crazy.
你
You, um…
那是巴纳还是诺顿（两部电影的男主角名字）
Bana or Norton?
不 电影里的那种太恐怖了
Oh, no. those movies were terrible.
是电视剧版的绿巨人
The tv hulk.
卢·费雷格诺吗
Lou Ferrigno?
没错
Yes.
- 满头小罗发型的那个卢·费雷格诺 - 没错
- Spiky-hair Lou Ferrigno? - Yes.
噢 你们一定以为我疯了
Oh, you think I'm crazy.
没有
No. uh…
不是 我 只不过是 是
No, I-it's just … is …
有没有
Is there, uh…
有没有什么原因
Would there be any reason.
以致于那个卢·费雷格诺 绿巨人
That Lou Ferrigno, the incredible hulk,
跟你丈夫有结怨呢
Um, would have a grudge against your husband?
没
No.
（惠灵顿卫报 当地人遭遇熊攻击毙命）
查到什么了吗
Find anything?
我亲自去看了下案发的房子
Well, uh, I saw the house.
怎样
And?
那儿有一个巨大的8英尺宽的洞
And there is a giant 8-foot-wide hole.
就在前门上
Where the front door used to be.
- 就像是 - 绿巨人挖的洞
- Almost like… - A hulk-sized hole.
也许吧 你又找到了什么呢
Maybe. what do you got?
噢 我发现比尔·伦道夫脾气相当的坏
Well, it turns out that Bill Randolph had quite the temper.
他曾有两次因婚姻暴力入罪 还多次在酒吧闹事
Uh, he's got two counts of spousal battery, bar brawls,
并被法院强制进行情绪管理
And court-ordered anger-management sessions.
可以说他一生气来就完全不是他本人了
You might say you wouldn't like him when he's angry.
也就是说 现实中一个暴躁之人被电视剧中最暴躁的角色杀了
So, a hothead getting killed by tv's greatest hothead.
听起来似乎罪有应得 不是吗
Kind of sounds like just deserts, doesn't it?
那就有点儿头绪来了
It's all starting to make sense.
有什么头绪啊
How is it starting to make sense?
在犯罪现场我还发现了别的一些东西
Well, I found something else at the crime scene.
一堆糖纸
Candy wrappers.
而且是很大一堆
Lots of 'em.
罪有应得 爱吃甜食
Just deserts, sweet tooth,
在杀人前会先吓死他们
Screwing with people before you kill them.
是恶作剧精灵 对不
We're dealing with the trickster, aren't we?
八九不离十了
Sure looks like.
太好了
Good.
我真是迫不及待地想手刃了这家伙
Been wanting to gank that mother since mystery spot.
真的吗
You sure?
没错
Yeah, I'm sure.
我是说 你确定要杀了他
No, I mean, are you sure you want to kill him?
那个贱人当时对我
Son of a bitch didn't think twice about icing me …
千刀万剐的时候可没犹豫 - 我知道
A thousand times. - No, I know.
- 我只是确认一下 - 那你什么意思
- I…I mean, i'm just saying. - What are you saying?
你是不想杀了他 还是怎么
If you don't want to kill him, then what?
- 和他谈谈 - 什么
- Talk to him. - What?
听着 仔细想想 迪恩
Look, think about it, Dean.
他是我们见过的最强大的生物之一
He's one of the most powerful creatures we've ever met.
或许我们能利用他
Maybe we can use him.
为了什么
For what?
恶作剧精灵是个享乐主义者 是吧
Okay, Trickster's like a … like a hugh hefner type, right?
莺歌艳舞 美女美酒
Wine, women, song.
也许他不想让世界毁灭
Maybe he doesn't want the party to end.
也许他和我们一样 都讨厌
I mean, maybe he hates this "angels.
所谓的天使恶魔大战
and demons" stuff as much as we do.
也许他会帮我们
Maybe he'll help us.
- 此话当真 - 当然
- You're serious? - Yeah.
与恶作剧精灵联盟
Ally with the trickster?
没错
Yeah.
那个血腥暴力的怪物
A bloody, violent monster…
你想和他成为朋友 欢乐地聊天吗
And you want to be facebook friends with him?
亏你想得出来 萨米
Nice, Sammy.
世界濒临毁灭 迪恩
The world is gonna end, Dean.
我们没工夫纠结道德立场
We don't have the luxury of a moral stand.
我只是说 这值得一试 仅此而已
I'm just saying, it's worth a shot. that's all.
如果不管用 我们再杀了他
If it doesn't work… we'll kill him.
不管怎样 我们怎么找他
How we gonna find the guy, anyway?
他不会只干一件就罢休 是吧
Well, he never takes just one victim, right?
他会现身的
He'll show.
呼叫总台 6号公路 187号
Uh, dispatch? I got a possible 187.
旧造纸厂这儿有可疑情况
Out here at the old paper mill on route 6.
收到
Roger that.
什么情况 兄弟
What are you looking at, son?
说实话 沃尔特 我实在不知道
Honestly, Walt, I wouldn't even know.
该怎样形容过才合适
How to begin to describe what I'm seeing.
只管派人来
Just, um, send everybody.
保持冷静 待在车旁 后援就到
All right, stay calm, stay by your car, our's on their way.
听起来很诡异
That sounds weird.
确定是那家伙吗
Weird enough to be our guy?
这儿出了命案
There was a murder here…
却连警车和警察都没有
And there's no police cars … there's nobody.
你觉得怎样
How does that look to you?
糟糕透顶
Crappy.
搞毛啊
What the hell?
大夫
Doctor.
「医生」
"Doctor"?
大夫
Doctor.
- 正经点 - 怎么了
- Seriously? - What?
正经点吗 知道吗 你是才华横溢
Seriously, you're brilliant, you know that?
却是个才华横溢的懦夫
And a coward. you're a brilliant coward.
你在说什么
Uh, what are you talking about?
别装蒜
As if you don't know.
难以置信
I don't believe this.
啥
What?
那是皮科洛大夫
That was Dr. Piccolo.
谁
Who?
艾伦·皮科洛大夫
Dr. Ellen Piccolo.
认真又性感的医生 她在
The sexy-yet-earnest doctor at…
西雅图慈善医院工作
…Seattle Mercy Hospital.
迪恩
Uh, Dean…
你到底在说啥
What the hell are you talking about?
大夫装和性感实习生
The doctor getups. the … the … the sexy interns.
还有「严肃认真」那一套 这说得通了
The "seriouslys." it all makes sense.
通什么鬼 到底怎么回事
What makes sense? what's going on?
我们在「性感医生」电视剧里
We're in "Dr. Sexy, M.D."
- 哥们儿 搞什么鬼 - 我不知道
- Dude, what the hell? - I don't know.
- 正经地说 到底搞什么鬼 - 我不知道
- No, seriously. what the hell? - I don't know.
随便说点什么也好
One theory. any theory.
恶作剧精灵把我们困在电视世界里了
Uh, the trickster trapped us in TV land.
你这样认为就蠢到家了
That's your theory? that's stupid.
你说我们在「性感医生」电视剧里的
You're the one who said we're on "Dr. Sexy, M.D."
但才没有电视世界这种东西
Yeah, but TV land isn't TV land.
我是指电视节目得有演员 灯光和剧组人员
I mean, there's actors a-and lights and crew members.
- 知道吗 可这是真实的 - 不可能啊
- You know? this looks real. - It can't be.
迪恩 这怎么可能是真实的
Dean, how can this possibly be real?
我也不知道 行了吧
I don't know. all right?
那是王大夫
Oh, but there goes Dr. Wang,
性感而傲慢的外科大夫
The sexy-but-arrogant heart surgeon.
那是强尼·德莱克
And there's Johnny Drake.
他不是活人 而是存在于他人脑海中的鬼魂
Oh, he's not even alive. he's a ghost in the mind of…
是她 那位性感而神经质的医生
…of her, the sexy-but-neurotic doctor over there.
这个剧里为啥还有鬼魂
So, this show has ghosts? Why?
不清楚 不过这种设定更刺激
I don't know. It is compelling.
你不是说过你不是粉丝吗
I thought you said you aren't a fan.
我不是粉丝 真的不是
I'm not. I'm not.
哥们儿
Oh, boy.
咋了
What?
- 是他 - 谁
- It's him. - Who?
是他 是性感医生
It's him. it's dr. sexy.
大夫
Doctor.
你能不能给我一个合适的理由
You want to give me one good reason.
为何你违抗我的直接命令
Why you defied my direct order.
反对为比尔太太做试验性面部移植手术呢
To do the experimental face transplant on Mrs. Beale?
一个理由吗
One reason?
当然啦
Sure.
你不是性感医生
You're not Dr. Sexy.
你疯了吗
You're crazy.
是吗
Really?
因为我确定 性感医生的性感之处
'cause I swore part of what makes dr. sexy sexy.
在于他穿的是牛仔靴
Is the fact that he wears cowboys boots…
而不是什么网球鞋
Not tennis shoes.
还说你不是粉丝
Yeah, you're not a fan.
这叫幸灾乐祸
It's a guilty pleasure.
叫保安来
Call security.
随便你 伙计 但我们知道你的真面目
Yeah, go ahead, pal. see, we know what you are.
你们两个越发厉害了嘛
You guys are getting better.
快把我们弄出去
Get us the hell out of here.
如果不呢
Or what?
你们拿的木桩呢 大块头
Don't see your wooden stakes, big guy.
是你通过警方无线电说话吧 那是个陷阱
That was you on the police scanner, right? this is a trick.
拜托
Hello-o-o?
我可是恶作剧精灵啊
Trickster?
别这样嘛 听说你们两爷们到了镇上
Come on! I heard you two yahoos were in town.
- 就忍不住想找点乐子 - 我们到底在哪儿
- How could I resist? - Where the hell are we?
喜欢吗 绝对独家制作哦
You like it? it's all homemade.
专用布景 专用演员
My own sets, my own actors.
我叫它小小专用电视机
Call it my own little idiot box.
我们怎么出去
How do we get out?
伙计 这可真是个难题（美国流行问答节目）
That, my friend, is the $64 question.
不管怎样 我们只是
Whatever. we just …
我们得谈谈 我们需要你的帮助
We need to talk to you. we need your help.
我来猜猜
Let me guess.
你俩蠢蛋把世界搞得一团糟
You two muttonheads broke the world,
现在指望我来收拾吗
And you want me to sweep up your mess?
求你了
Please.
就五分钟 请听我们说
Just five minutes. hear us out.
当然 你猜怎么着
Sure. tell you what.
先活过这24小时 我们再谈
Survive the 24 next hours, we'll talk.
活过什么
Survive what?
游戏呀
The game.
什么游戏
What game?
你们身在其中
You're in it.
怎么玩
How do we play?
你们正在玩呢
You're playing it.
什么规则
What are the rules?
该死的杂种
Oh, son of a bitch.
性感医生
Dr. Sexy?
呼叫性感医生 请到急诊室
Paging Dr. Sexy. Report to the E.R.
顺便说一句 跟怪物谈话
Oh, by the way … talking with monsters?
真是好主意
Hell of a plan.
那 我们现在怎么做
Just… What do we do now?
知道我要做什么吗 走人
You know what I'm doing? Leaving.
女士 到底怎么了
Lady… What the hell?
你是个出色的 出色的
You are a brilliant, brilliant…
懦夫 你已经说过了
Yeah, a coward. You already said that.
但我有事情要告诉你
But I got news for you.
我不是医生
I am not a doctor.
不要这么说
Don't say that.
你是我见过的所有脑神经外科医生中
You are the finest cerebrovascular neurosurgeon.
最出色的的一个
I have ever met… And I have met plenty.
那姑娘死在你手术台上
So that girl died on your table.
不是你的错 不是任何人的错
It wasn't your fault. It wasn't anybody's fault.
人总是会死的
Sometimes people just die.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're saying to me.
你害怕了
You're afraid.
你害怕再做手术 害怕再去爱人
You're afraid to operate again, and you're afraid to love.
我们得离开这儿
Yeah, we're getting out of here.
医生
Hey, doctor.
什么事
Yes?
我妻子需要做面部移植手术
My wife needs that face transplant.
好吧 知道吗 兄弟
Okay. You know what, pal?
这一切都不是真的 明白吗
None of this is real, okay?
你妻子什么鬼东西也不需要
And your wife doesn't need jack squat.
懂了吗
Okay?
医生
Hey, doctor.
真的 是真的
Real! It's real!
这里需要医生
Hey! we need a doctor!
血压80到50 正在下降
B.P. is 80 over 50… and dropping.
医生
Doctor?
什么
What?
萨姆 做点儿什么 快
Sam, do something. Come on.
这堆东西我都不会用
I don't know how to use any of this crap.
学着用
Figure it out!
萨姆 快点儿 我等着呢
Sam! Come on. I'm waiting.
好吧 给我一把
Okay, um, I need a…
折刀 一些牙线
Penknife, some dental floss,
一根针 还有750毫升威士忌
A sewing needle, and a fifth of whiskey.
动起来
Stat!
怎么样了 好了没有
We okay? How's it looking?
很好 你会没事的
Yep. You'll be fine.
让我们来玩 「砸蛋大冒险」
Let's play "nut-cracker"!
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester…
你背弃亲哥哥选择的那个恶魔
What was the name of the demon.
她的名字是什么
You chose over your own brother?
倒计时
Countdown.
什么
What?
- 我该说什么 - 我怎么知道
- What am I supposed to say? - You think I know?
我 我听不懂 日语
Uh, I-I don't … I don't understand, uh, Japanese.
你背弃亲哥哥选择的那个恶魔
What was the name of the demon.
她的名字是什么
You chose over your own brother?
他是不是在耍我
Is he screwing with me?
我我我 我不会讲日语
I-I-I-I-I can't speak Japanese.
正确答案是
The answer is…
露比
Ruby.
我很抱歉 萨姆·温彻斯特
I'm sorry, Sam Winchester.
抱歉 为什么抱歉
Sorry? Sorry for what?
迪恩
Dean.
「砸蛋大冒险」
Whoa! "nut-cracker"!
萨姆
Sam?
什么
Yeah?!
千里先生
Hello, Chikato-san?
什么事
Hai?
我们有介绍过这种营养虾片吗
Have we discussed these nutritious Shrimp Chips?
营养丰富 味道好
Lots of nutrition, tastes great…
而且越吃越苗条 像你一样呦
And the more on eats, the slimmer they get just like you.
你没事吧
You okay?
欢迎购买
Please buy them.
又是什么
Now what?
卡西
Cass?
这也是恶作剧的一部分吗
Is this another trick?
是我 你们在这里做什么
It's me. Uh, what are you doing here?
我们 你在这里做什么
Us? What are you doing here?
我在找你们 你们杳无音信好多天了
Looking for you. You've been missing for days.
那就带我们离开这儿
Get us the hell out of here, then.
我们走
Let's go.
卡西
Cass.
不好 不好
No, no, no, no.
恶作剧精灵先生不喜欢漂亮男天使
Mr. Trickster does not like pretty-boy angels.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester…
如果你弟弟从没出生过
Would your Mother and Father sitll be alive…
你的父母是不是可能还活着
If your brother was never born?
倒数
Countdown.
我怎么办 我怎么办
What do I do? What do I do? I don't…
我可不想被敲
Want to get hit in the nuts.
我知道
I-I know. Uh, uh…
- 你就 等一下 - 什么
- Just, um… Wait. - What?!
- 我扮演的是医生 - 什么
- I played a doctor. - What?
「性感医生」里 我扮演的是医生
In… in "Dr. Sexy." I played a doctor.
- 我给你做了手术 - 那又怎样
- I operated. - So?
我演了恶作剧精灵让我演的角色
So, I played the role the Trickster wanted me to play.
或许我们应该继续
M-maybe we just have to go along with it.
- 继续什么 - 继续游戏
- Go along with what? - With the game.
我是说 这是个问答节目
I mean, we're on a game show, right?
那就回答问题
So, just answer the question.
- 用日语吗 - 对
- In Japanese? - Yeah.
- 我不懂日语 - 试试
- I don't know Japanese! - Try!
该死
Damn it!
答案是
The answer is…
是的
Yes?
Yes.
迪恩·温彻斯特 「砸蛋大冒险」冠军
Dean Winchester … "nut-cracker" champion!
你怎么做到的
How did you do that!
我也不知道
I have no idea.
就是这样了
So, that's it.
演好自己的角色 就能活下去
We play our roles, we survive.
是啊 要演多久
Yeah. Play our roles for how long?
问得好
Good question.
我患了生殖器疱疹
I've got genital herpes.
来真的
Seriously?
是你说演好自己角色的
Hey, you're the one who said play our roles.
我患了生殖器疱疹
I've got genital herpes.
我试着负起责任
I tried to be responsible.
我试过
Did I try.
现在我每天服用两次「疱疹清」
But now I take twice-daily Herpexia.
以减小传染给他人的风险
To reduce my chances of passing it on.
向你的医生咨询如何服用「疱疹清」
Ask your doctor about using Herpexia.
在服用「疱疹清」前 一定要
Patients should always consult with a physician.
咨询医嘱
Before using Herpexia.
可能的副作用包括
Possible side effects include.
头痛 腹泻 永久性勃起功能障碍
Headache, diarrhea, permanent erectile dysfunction,
恶心还有自杀的想法
Thoughts of suicide, and nausea.
我做了一切我能做的
I am doing all I can.
略微减轻生殖器疱疹的传播
To slightly lessen the spread of genital herpes.
这是好事
And that's a good thing.
他娘的
Son of a bitch!
我真的非常抱歉
I am really, really very sorry,
但是
But…
我们还有些事要做
…we've got some work to do.
但我们也有事要做
But we did do work…
更深入的
In depth.
我们还要做这个做多久啊
How long do we have to keep doing this?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许一辈子
Maybe forever?
我们大概会死在这儿了
We might die in here.
很好笑吗
How is that funny?
这群贪婪的人
Vultures.
你还好吧
You okay?
- 我没有太多的时间 - 发生了什么事
- I don't have much time. - What happened?
- 我离开了 - 从哪里
- I got out. - From where?
听我说 有些事不对劲
Listen to me. something is not right.
这东西比它本来强大得多
This thing is much more powerful than it should be.
什么东西 那个恶作剧精灵吗 - 如果他是个恶作剧精灵的话
What thing … the trickster? if it is a trickster.
什么意思
What do you mean?
大家好
Hello!
谢谢
Thank you!
Thank you.
停停
Stop.
你好 卡西迪奥
Hi, castiel.
- 你认识他啊 - 你刚才把他送哪去了
- You know him? - Where did you just send him?
放轻松 他会活着的
Relax. he'll live.
也许吧
Maybe.
把我当猴耍 对吧 我们了解
I'm done with the monkey dance, okay? we get it.
你了解什么了 神童
Yeah? get what, hotshot?
我们扮演的角色 对吧 那是你的游戏吧
Playing our roles, right? that's your game?
- 那一半是游戏 - 那另一半是什么
- That's half the game. - What's the other half?
向那边扮演你们的角色
Play your roles out there.
这又是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
你知道的 萨姆 扮演路西法
You know … sam, starring as lucifer.
迪恩 扮演米迦勒
Dean, starring as michael.
你们两人死斗 扮演你们的角色
Your celebrity deathmatch. play your roles.
你想我们答应那些混蛋
You want us to say yes to those sons of bitches?
没错 让我们点亮生命的希望
Hells, yeah. let's light this candle!
我们那么做 这个世界就要完了
We do that, the world will end.
是吗 那是谁的过失
Yeah? and whose fault is that?
谁释放了路西法
Who popped lucifer out of the box, hmm?
听着 这才开始 你让它开始的
Look, it's started. you started it.
它不可能停下来的 所以让我们做完它吧
It can't be stopped. so, let's get it over with.
天堂还是地狱 你站哪边
Heaven or hell … which side you on?
我不在任何一边
I'm not on either side.
对哦
Yeah, right.
你是选择跟米迦勒还是路西法
You're grabbing ankle for michael or lucifer.
是哪个呢
Which one is it?
你给我听好 你这个自大狂
You listen to me, you arrogant dick.
我不为任何一个混蛋做事 相信我
I don't work for either of those s.o.b.s, believe me.
你是某人的贱人
Hmm. oh, you're somebody's bitch.
永远不要以为你已经知道我是什么了
Don't you ever, ever presume to know what I am.
现在仔细听好
Now, listen very closely.
这里将要发生什么
Here's what's gonna happen.
你们要适应 承担你们的责任
You're gonna suck it up, accept your responsibilities,
扮演好命运所选的角色
And play the roles that destiny has chosen for you.
如果我们不同意呢
And if we don't?
那你们将要待在这个电视里了
Then you'll stay here in tv land…
永远的
Forever.
300个频道
300 channels and, uh, nothing's on.
天哪
Oh, come on.
你怎么想的
What do you think?
问我想的什么吗
What do I think?
我想去你的 这就是我想的
I think go screw yourself, that's what I think.
你给我们点时间 好吗
Uh, can you give us a sec, please?
谢谢
Thanks.
- 你要冷静点儿 - 冷静吗
- You got to calm down. - Calm down?
我晚上戴着墨镜
I am wearing sunglasses at night.
你知道谁干的 就是那个零智商的混蛋
You know who does that? no-talent douche bags.
我讨厌这个游戏
I hate this game.
我讨厌我们这个警察节目
I hate that we're in a procedural cop show.
你想知道为什么吗
And you want to know why?
因为我讨厌警匪片
Because I hate procedural cop shows!
他们将近有300个节目在电视里滚动播放
There's like 300 of them on television.
他们都是
they're all the??
都是像 看啊 那里一架飞机失事了 真蛋疼
It's, "ooh, a plane crashed here." oh, shut up!
- 嘿 - 干嘛
- Hey. - What?
去看看那个甜食主义者
Check out sweet tooth over there.
就那家伙
Think that's him?
跟我来
Just, uh, follow my lead.
你们有问题吗
You, uh, you okay?
是
Yeah.
有没有什么发现
What do we got?
除了脖子有明显被勒的痕迹
Well, aside from the ligature marks around his neck,
在其他地方
has what appears to be.
咽喉下方有血块样
A roll of quarters jammed down his throat.
要我说
Well, I say…
他中彩了
Jackpot.
另外
Also…
在腹部有一处戳伤
There was a stab wound to the lower abdomen there.
要我说
Well, I say…
不入虎穴，焉得虎子
…no guts, no glory.
把这人的胃给拿走了
Get that guy a…Tums.
星际保龄球？
Gutter ball.
真不错 伙计们
That's a good one, guys.
你们杀错人了 蠢货们
You got the wrong guy, idiot.
我很担心 伙计
I'm worried, man …
那个混蛋会对卡西下毒手
What that s.o.b. did to cass.
他在哪儿
You know, where is he?
萨姆
Sam?
你在哪儿
Where are you?
我是萨姆 给我留言
It's sam. leave me a message.
萨姆 是我
Sam, it's me.
你他妈的去哪里了
Where the hell did you go?
迪恩
Dean?
萨姆
Sam?
你在哪儿
Where are you?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我的老天
Oh, crap.
我们并没干掉恶作剧精灵
I don't think we killed the trickster.
木桩没起作用
Okay, stake didn't work.
- 那么另一个木桩 - 我理解不能
- So, what? this another trick? - I don't know.
也许没起作用的原因是那个根本不是那个混蛋
Maybe the stake didn't work because it's not a trickster.
- 什么意思 - 你听卡西说
- What do you mean? - I mean, you heard cass.
他曾说过这个家伙比恶作剧精灵更强力
He said this thing was too powerful to be a trickster.
还有他为什么老是盯着卡西
Yeah, and did you notice the way he looked at cass?
应该卡西了解他
Almost like he knew him.
当我们说起米伽勒和路西法的时候
And how pissed he got.
看他有多愤怒
When you brought up michael and lucifer.
- 这个混蛋 - 怎么了
- Son of a bitch. - What?
我想我知道和我们对着干的家伙了
I think I know what we're dealing with.
- 迪恩 - 怎么了
- Dean? - What?
我感觉很不爽
That, um, feels really uncomfortable.
你确定这能奏效
You sure this is gonna work?
没 不过除了这我没法子了
No, but I have no other ideas.
好吧 你这个混球
All right, you son of a bitch!
叔
Uncle!
我们做到了
We'll do it!
我该按喇叭么
Should I honk?
萨姆 瞧你多有轮廓美啊
Sam, get a load of the rims on you.
咬我啊
Eat me.
孩子们 准备好静静地离开了吗
Okay, boys, ready to go quietly?
等等 等等 别那么快
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Not so fast.
在萨姆不能对人竖中指前 谁都不能离开
Nobody's going anywhere until Sam has opposable thumbs.
这样有区别么
What's the difference?
无论如何撒旦也会骑在他屁屁上的
Satan's gonna ride his ass one way or another.
开心了
Happy?
回答我一个问题 为什么木桩没杀死你
Tell me one thing. Why didn't the stake kill you?
我是恶作剧精灵啊
I am the trickster.
或许你根本不是
But maybe you're not.
或许你一直就是天使
Maybe you've always been an angel.
是什么
A what?!
孩子 是不是有人给你们糖吃了
Somebody slip a mickey in your power shake, kid?
我说吧
I'll tell you what.
你尽管跳出这团圣火
You just jump out of the holy fire,
我们随后就赔礼道歉
And we'll call it our mistake.
演得好 小伙子们 演得好
Well played, boys. Well played.
你们从哪弄来的圣油
Where'd you get the holy oil?
可以说这是从萨姆屁股里抽出来的
Oh, you might say we pulled it out of Sam's ass.
我哪里露馅了
Where'd I screw up?
你没有
You didn't.
但除了你 没别人能把卡西那样摆平的
But nobody gets the jump on Cass like you did.
按你们的说法这叫哈米吉多顿（世界末日善恶决战的战场）
Mostly, it was the way you talked about armageddon.
言下之意是
Meaning?
以鄙人之见
Well, call it personal experience.
只有被谈及他们的家族时
Nobody gets that angry.
他们才会如此愤怒
Unless they're talking about their own family.
那么你是哪个 性情暴躁的 爱打喷嚏的 还是那个唠叨的老婆娘
So, which one are you? grumpy, sneezy, or douchey?
我是加百列 满意了
Gabriel, okay?
他们管我叫加百列
They call me Gabriel.
加百列 大天使
Gabriel? the archangel?
惭愧
Guilty.
好吧 加百列 大天使是怎么沦落成恶作剧精灵的
Okay, Gabriel. How does an archangel become a trickster?
自我申辩加保护
My own private witness protection.
我带着会变脸的本领 从天堂坠落于凡间
I skipped out of heaven, had a face transplant,
开拓属于我的一个小世界
Carved out my own little corner of the world…
直到你们俩来毁了这一切
Till you two screwed it all up.
天父知道你逃走 又转变信仰以后
And what did daddy say when you.
他是什么意见
Ran off and join in the paynims?
天父持保留意见
Daddy doesn't say anything about anything.
然后呢 为何你要弃他而去
Then what happened? Why'd you ditch?
你心里怪他吗
Well, do you blame him?
我是说 他的弟兄都是重量级的家伙
I mean, his brothers are heavyweight douche-nozzles.
闭嘴
Shut your cake hole.
你根本不了解我的家族
You don't know anything about my family.
我挚爱我父 我的弟兄们 曾经很爱他
I loved my father, my brothers … loved them.
但看看他们对彼此的所作所为
But watching them turn on each other?
互相厮杀
Tear at each other's throats?
我简直忍无可忍
I couldn't bear it, okay?!
所以我才离开了
So I left.
现在这一切正在重演
And now it's happening all over again.
那你要协助我们阻止这一切
Then help us stop it.
有去无回了
It can't be stopped.
你想眼睁睁看着世界末日的到来吗
You want to see the end of the world?
我是想结束一切
I want it to be over!
拜你们所赐
I have to sit back.
我就是要坐山观虎斗
And watch my own brothers kill.
眼睁睁看着我的亲兄弟互相残杀
each other, thach other，thanks you two.
天使 地狱 我无所谓谁赢谁输
Heaven, hell … I don't care who wins!
我只想一切尽早结束
I just want it to be over!
事情不一定会发展成那样的
Well, it doesn't have to be like that.
一定还有什么办法能挽救的
There has to be some way to … to pull the plug.
你真是一点都不了解我的家族
Oh, you do not know my family.
你们所谓的天启
What you guys call the apocalypse.
我习惯叫他周日晚餐
I used to call sunday dinner.
之所以不能阻止这一切的到来
That's why there's no stopping this …
是因为这关乎于一场战争
Because this isn't about a war.
关乎于互相深爱的弟兄
It's about two brothers that loved each other.
最后反目成仇的战争
And betrayed each other.
你们肯定认为 好像你们也被牵连进来了
You think you'd be able to relate.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你们真该道个歉 两个混蛋
You sorry sons of bitches.
你们觉得为什么皮囊偏偏是你们俩
Why do you think you two are the vessels?
好好想想吧
Think about it.
米迦勒 兄长
Michael … the big brother,
忠实于那位并不在身边的父亲
Loyal to an absent father.
路西法 最小的弟弟
And Lucifer … the little brother,
总是反抗父亲的计划
Rebellious of daddy's plan.
你们生来如此 小伙子们
You were born to this, boys.
这就是你们的命运
It's your destiny!
至始至终就是你们
It was always you!
愿父的旨意行在地上
As it is in heaven…
如同行在天上
So it must be on earth.
兄弟俩只能留一个
One brother has to kill the other.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you saying?
你们认为 为什么我会对你们这么感兴趣的
Why do you think I've always taken such an interest in you?
因为在不久前
Because from the moment.
天父在这里失去理智
Dad flipped on the lights around here,
我们就知道你们将会来结束这一切
We knew it was all gonna end with you.
一直是
Always.
不会
No.
不可能的
That's not gonna happen.
很遗憾
I'm sorry…
但事实如此
But it is.
伙计们 这若真是一部电视剧就好了
Guys, I wish this were a tv show.
简单的问答 鞠躬谢幕
Easy answers, endings wrapped up in a bow.
但事实摆在眼前
But this is real.
我们将会用鲜血结束一切
And it's gonna end bloody for all of us.
事情毫无疑问会这样发展
That's just how it's got to be.
小伙子们
So, boys…
现在怎么办
Now what?
用仅有的余生凝视彼此吗
Stare at each other for the rest of eternity?
首先
Well, first of all,
你得马上把卡西弄回来
You're gonna bring Cass back from wherever you stashed him.
我非做不可么
Oh, am I?
当然
Yeah.
不然我们把你泡在圣油里
Or we're going to dunk you in some holy oil.
然后油炸大天使
And deep-fry ourselves an archangel.
卡西 你没事吧
Cass, you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
你好啊 加百列
Hello, Gabriel.
你好 兄弟
Hey, bro.
寻父之旅如何啊
How's the search for daddy going?
让我猜猜 糟糕透顶
Let me guess. Awful.
我们离开这儿
Okay, we're out of here.
走吧 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
好吧
Okay.
伙计们
Hey … guys?
这算什么
So … so, what?
你们打算把我禁锢在这儿一辈子吗
You're just gonna … you're gonna leave me here forever?
不会
No. we're not.
我们跟你不一样
'cause we don't screw with people the way you do.
我声明一下
And for the record…
这绝不是你们弟兄间的拳击赛
This isn't about some prizefight between your brothers.
或者某某命运我们不可逆转
Or some destiny that can't be stopped!
这就是你
This is about you.
不敢抵抗你的家族而已
Being too afraid to stand up to your family!
别说你没对我们做过什么
Don't say I never did anything for you.
他滔滔不绝讲的那些
All that stuff he was spouting in there …
你觉得可信吗
You think he was telling the truth?
反正他是置信不疑
I think he believes it.
那我们现在怎么办
So, what do we do?
不知道
I don't know.
告诉你
I'll tell you one thing.
这会儿我还真希望我在演电视剧
Right about now, I wish I was back on a tv show.
嗯 我也是
Yeah, me too.